♫ In the not too distant future
somewhere in time and space
♫ Mike Nelson and his robot
pals are caught in a nasty place
♫ They try to survive the wrath of Pearl,
♫ just an evil gal who
wants to rule the world
♫ From her castle below
she sets her sights above
♫ just to torture all her
captives on the satellite of love
♫ Get me down
♫ I'll send him cheesy
movies, the worst I can find
♫ La la la
♫ He'll have to sit and watch them all
♫ and I'll monitor his mind
♫ La la la
♫ Now keep in mind Mike can't
control where the movies
♫ begin or end, la la la
♫ He'll try to keep his sanity
♫ with the help of his robot friends
♫ Robot roll call
♫ Cambot: you're on, Gypsy: oh my stars
♫ Tom Servo: check me
out, Crow, I'm different
♫ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
♫ And other science facts, la la la
♫ Just repeat to
yourself, it's just a show
♫ I should really just relax
♫ For Mystery Science Theater 3000 ♫
(acoustic guitar strums)
(door slamming
(booming echo)
(beeping, motor whirring)
(clinking metal and a loud bang)
(rapid screech and wooshing air)
(hissing air)
(clanking gears)
- Hi everyone, Mike Nelson
here on the Satellite of Love,
this is Tom Servo and
Tom's got something to say.
- Thank you Mike (clears throat)
Mike, folks, in 1984 the
techno-mega-giant band named Yes
released a song in which
they assured us that:
♫ the owner of a lonely
heart is much better than
♫ the owner of a broken heart ♫
- Yeah great song, I remember that.
- As do we all Mike, as do we all.
But my point is simply
this, they introduced
a profound topic and then
barely scratched the surface.
They told me nothing, how does:
♫ The owner of a lonely heart ♫
compare to say the:
♫ Owner of a broken gas fireplace ♫
or for that matter to the,
♫ Owner of a perfectly
functional cheese slicer
♫ As the owner of a lonely heart ♫
How do I stack up against the,
♫ Owner of a pencil ♫
I mean come on Yes!
- I don't think it's up to Yes to come up
with every possible permutation.
- Well they brought it up Mike
and there's so much more to consider!
What about the,
♫ owner of a parcel of land in Montana ♫
versus the,
♫ owner of a pie ♫
- We'll be right back
- [Tom] How does the
♫ owner of a jar ♫
stack up against the
♫ owner of a split level ♫
(upbeat keyboard music)
- Okay now we've done it, every time
we say owner of a lonely
heart (fast keyboard flourish)
we get a Yes orchestra hit.
- Alright, hang on, test,
test, owner of a lonely heart.
(fast keyboard flourish)
- Well for now, let's just avoid
owner of a, you know
- [Crow] Lonely heart.
- Right. (fast keyboard flourish)
(all grunt and groan together)
- Ah, yes pearl?
- Nelson thank goodness it's you,
I needed to talk to a loser!
(laughter)
Oh we have fun, don't we brain guy?
- Oh we do, we, we really do.
- But you know, anyone can.
- That's right, you see I've realized that
with the large staff necessary
to taking over the world,
I need to keep the
workplace loose and fun.
And studies show that if I do,
you morons will be more
productive. (laughing)
- Hey you want some
tips on how to have fun?
You should see this place
on a Friday. (laughs)
- Yeah, it is nuts! (laughs)
- I'm sure, well let's get started.
- I mean sometimes I think
everyone up here is crazy!
- Yeah I tell my friends,
I'm not sure whether I work
on a satellite or at the nut house!
(Mike and Tom Servo laugh)
- Okay, let's try and
keep to our schedule.
- I'll tell you who is funny, Crow.
Crow is the cutup around here. (laughs)
- [Crow] Oh come on.
[Tom] Don't drink milk
and talk to this fellow, or
it will come out your nose!
- No come on.
- Look, shut up!
Okay, why don't we start
with an illustration
of how humor can lighten up
a stressful situation, Brain Guy?
- Oh, sure. (clears throat)
Excuse me Pearl, business, business,
deadline, merger, merger,
stock option, acquisition
- [Pearl] I'm sorry what was
that I'm busy having eyeballs that won't
stay in their sockets!
(laughing)
- Do you begin to see how creativity
can lead to productivity?
- Um no, I'm just kinda depressed.
- Yeah mostly, I feel sad
and achey. (Tom Servo grunts)
- Well I'm glad you had fun.
Bobo, let's send them their movie.
Final Justice starring the
dyspeptic Joe Don Baker.
- As soon as I'm done wearing
big, funny, goofy teeth.
- Hey, get to work!
What the hell do you think
this is, clown college?
You make me pah-yuke!
(bobo whines and grunts)
- Wow, I'm terrified and delighted.
(all laughing)
(buzzing)
(door hissing, skittering)
(echoing impact)
(wooshing air)
(thudding impact and clinking metal)
(dripping)
(whirring gears)
(beeping followed by door clanging)
(clanking metal)
♫ here we are on the radio ♫
- [Crow] Oh weird.
- [Mike] Oh man.
- [Tom] Oh boy, cowboy music
let's just turn back shall we?
- [Mike] No, no we can't.
Sit right there.
- [Voiceover] Heavy rain continuing
through the night, clearing tomorrow.
And now here's an update on
the car bombing in Dallas.
- [Crow] Oh yeah.
- [Voiceover] Building
contractor Larry Wayne
(crow gasps)
is in critical condition
at Parkland Hospital.
The Texas Ranger Organized
Crime Unit is investigating.
Good luck boys and now back to our music.
- Oh I wish I was illiterate
so I didn't have to read that.
♫ The world I know is dyin
♫ Fadin before its time ♫
- [Tom] Please can't I
have just one more justice?
♫ To me it's just ♫
- [Tom] He came, he saw, he
acted with Bill McKinney.
♫ You can call me what you will ♫
- Sounds like they
hired Livingston Taylor.
♫ Life don't feel the same no more ♫
- Is he dead? Hey?
- [Tom] Hey, Rossano Brazzi!
- Some enchanted evening!
- Man is it pourin our there TJ!
- [Geronimo] Yeah. (grunts)
- How we doin tonight, anything happen?
- [Geronimo] No calls.
- Not nuthin?
- Naw a big fat, nadda.
- [Tom] That's me.
- Listen TJ there's
somethin I've been meanin
to talk to yah about.
- [Geronimo] Yeah?
- How's the diet comin?
- What are yah mah mother?
- No TJ, what I am is your friend.
- And Jimmy Dean.
- And you know you got
less than three months
before your next annual.
- I'll make it.
- Not unless you get off
yer, and get some exercise
and you stop eatin those damn donuts.
- [Tom] And quit drinkin baby oil.
♫ maybe, it's just me
♫ you can call me what you will ♫
- [Tom] Call her Guido Sarducci.
- An editor they scrape from the bottom
of the barrel every spring.
(car horns blaring, tires squealing)
- [Tom] Road hog!
- [Mike] The D-P is an Austrian prince.
(suspenseful music)
- Oh Tom Wolfe, great.
(men arguing in a foreign language)
- [Tom] Executive Producer, The Sun King.
(man speaking rapidly
in a foreign language)
- [Mike] I'm really sorry, I can't
make another claim on my insurance.
- [Tom] Greydon Clark the producer
of hobgoblins, we're doomed!
- [Crow] Oh, man. (groans)
- Boss, hurry!
- Yeah if you're gonna wack
a guy, get a decent battery.
- [Mike] Mmm hmm.
- We just (slurs excitedly) come on!
- [Tom] Yeah let's get out the manual.
If you've killed someone, turn to page 37.
- Listen, we're near the border.
- [Dark Suited Man] If
we get out of Texas,
we're safe, right?
- Oh here boss, if you've killed someone
and you have our limited
edition, turn to page 43.
- [Don] You know you're the
most qualified deputy sheriff in
the whole damn state.
- [Crow] What the hell is this?
- All them years up in
Dallas and that training
must be worth somethin.
- Dallas wasn't all my
fault, I didn't kill
all those people all by myself.
- Most of em.
- I bagged my limit that
day, that's fer sure.
- [Mike] Killin rules.
- Course you know, TJ I
think I uh, mighta kept
the senator's brother out of it.
- Eh he was doin dirty.
He pays the price just
like all us ordinary folk.
- Yeah, so you get booted
outta Dallas and I end up
with the best deputy sheriff in Texas.
- That's our back story.
- Somehow just don't seem fair.
- Well Momma never said life was fair.
- [Tom] Pass the sausage.
- I pay the price.
- Listen man, I'm gonna
go see the old lady.
You take care, if anything
happens give me a call.
- Alright.
- Get some sleep, alright?
- Yeah
- [Mike] And put a glade
air freshener in here okay?
- Oh Bob, wait a minute.
- Yeah?
- Photos came back from the drug store.
- They're pictures of my lunch yesterday.
- Look at that.
- [Tom] Look how nude I am.
- Isn't that nice?
- Yeah, Trevor's a cute kid alright.
You're a lucky man Bob.
- [Crow] Uh oh.
- Hey, who's out there messin with
that car on a night like this?
- [Crow] Mm hmm.
- Hey hold it right there you guys!
(gunshot)
Hold it right there!
(Tom Servo snorts)
- [Crow] Yep.
(gunshots and ricochets ring out)
- [Tom] Hey that was the same shot.
- [Crow] Exact same.
- [Tom] So what goes on in Texas?
Opening fire on cops, killing Presidents,
the whole Bush thing,
I mean what the hell?
- [Crow] The brisket is in the (groans)
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Oh my heart's
shuttin down again, hang on.
- [Mike] It'll be a lot of
fun to shoot at him now.
I mean he's gonna die anyway.
- [Crow] He just bleached his
hair and shaped it into a hat.
(suspenseful music)
[Tom] It's, It Happened
One Night, only gay.
- You killed a cop!
- Listen, would you rather explain to them
what we are doing out here
in the middle of nowhere?
Come on the border's got
to be somewhere near here.
- [Mike] Strange Texas drawl.
- [Crow] Mm hmm.
- Once we are beyond the
States, we'll be free.
And then it's Europe, kiddo!
It's Europe, let's go! Come on!
- [Crow] The sun is blotted out
as Joe Don Baker approaches.
- [Tom] Alright, halt or I'll fart.
- [Mike] Can he prove he's not Boyd Aston?
- [Tom] I don't think so.
- [Crow] Ah, now it all becomes, huh?
(thrilling guitar music)
- [Mike] Music from the
police woman soundtrack.
We have to cross the river into Italy.
- Hey, this is it Tony!
We found it, the border.
Look!
- [Crow] He found a Taco Bell? Big Deal.
- [Tom] First time water has hit
his pants in over a year.
- [Mike] At least from the outside.
(tom servo clicking tongue rapidly)
- [Crow] The guy on the
right is from the nah.
- Hold it, right there!
- [Mike] Now over four inches, good.
- Relax Tony, he's got no authority here.
- [Tom] He's got all Dorothy here.
- You can do nothing to us.
You are American.
We are across the border!
- That border don't mean, to
me, just a line in the dirt.
- [Mike] Quick distract
him with a mostaccioli.
- You think you can take me?
Go ahead on.
- [Crow] He's sweating palm kernel oil.
- It's your move.
- [Tom] Uh, him or me?
- [Tom] Look, his chest hair's on fire.
- [Tom] I just want a lah-ser-oni.
(groans and screams)
- [Crow] In the time it takes him to fall,
the government in Italy
changes three times.
- You son of a!
- [Crow] What?
- [Tom] What is he a son of?
A preacher man, son of
a son of a sailor maybe?
- [Crow] He absorbed all the water.
- Tony!
(chuckling)
- [Crow] Tony.
- Tony!
- Hey!
- You son of a!
- [Tom] Something!
- You don't have the right to do this!
- I got all the right I need.
Now get off your knees you son of a!
- [Mike] Same thing you said.
- Come on you yella bellied!
Go for it! I want you to draw, come on!
What's the matter?
Shootin people from the
dark more your style?
You think you can take me, go ahead on!
- [Crow] Here's my meaty flank.
- It's your move.
- You'll pay for my
brother! I swear you'll pay!
- Scavenger.
- If you killed my
brother, I'd barbecue you.
Now get up and go for your gun!
- You'll see my gun, when the time comes!
I swear on God you're gonna pay for this!
- [Tom] I'll kill you,
but I won't curse you.
- The man you killed back
there was my partner.
I oughta kill you on general principle.
Instead I'm gonna take
you to Texas and justice.
You got the right to remain silent.
(groans)
- [Tom] Oh, he is a real cop.
- And all that other stuff.
(upbeat keyboard music)
- [Voiceover] Thomas Jefferson
Ronald the third, Apache.
- [Crow] It's god.
- That's pronounced Geronimo.
- An Apache Texas sheriff?
What's this world comin too?
Now you'll be working with the
Italian authorities on this,
so just do as you're told.
My god this is gonna be a wonderful piece
of international PR.
- It's not my job to
extradite, I'm a deputy sheriff
not a border patrol agent.
- [Crow] Ma made me a real cowboy suit.
- Normally I would but
you're sort of a hero
to the Italians, you
know a big Texas sheriff
and all, they want to personally thank you
for capturing this guy.
- What do I get out of this?
- A medal.
- A medal?
- [Mike] Like zinc?
- That oughta frost their,
in Dallas. (chuckles)
- [Crow] You're so noble.
- Well you see Mr. Palermo's
been a major source
of embarrassment to
the Italian government.
- [Mike] That's hard to do.
- He's made contracts in four
continents, that we know of.
- Been a busy boy, huh?
- [Tom] Oh hi.
- I get around Cowboy.
Hey, what makes you think
you can handle a guy like me?
- [Tom] Uh huh?
- You don't know anything,
you're going to Europe.
- [Crow] Do you know how
harsh the toilet paper
is over there?
- (speaks in a foreign language)
- Hmph?
- [Palermo] (speaks in a foreign language)
- [Mike] Yeah, lickin ze me.
- If I'd known you was gonna
be such a fuss, I'd have
dusted your back on the
border when I had the chance.
- [Crow] You son of a.
- Oh you'll get your chance Cowboy.
You can make a book on it.
- [Tom] It would be called:
getting your chance.
- Just turn Mr. Palermo
here over to the Italian
authorities, get them to sign him off,
and you can go back to
Texas and enjoy yourself.
Who knows, you might like Europe.
- [Crow] Guests of Final Justice fly TWA.
(cheerful string music)
- Darling what is your name?
- [Geronimo] No thanks.
- [Mike] It's Butch.
- Shut up.
- [Tom] John Lovitz refuses a drink.
- [Crow] As does Andy Warhol.
(sinister horn music)
- [Tom] Let's talk loudly about our SUVs.
(dramatic music) (beeping sound)
- [Tom] This reminds the pilot
he's been a failure in life.
- I'll announce it.
- [Crow] Ladies and
gentleman, I'm a failure.
- Ladies and gentleman,
this is your pilot speaking.
We're experiencing some
technical difficulties.
Nothing to be alarmed
about, however we will not
be preceding on to Sicily.
We will be landing at the
nearest island, Malta.
- Stewardess.
- [Mike] Get out another meal.
- Where the hell's Malta?
- It's a beautiful island nearby.
- So, like Galveston?
- [Tom] Yes, plenty of room
for development in Malta!
- [Crow] Malta, makers of fine
crosses, knights and falcons!
- Uh mam,
- [Tom] Can I have another meal?
- When's this plane gonna
be ready to go to Sicily?
- I'm sorry sir.
It appears not until tomorrow.
We have made arrangements
for overnight accommodations.
You must speak to customs.
- [Mike] So, so no meal?
- Just great. Here you go.
- [Voiceover] Air Malta flight
110 now departing for London,
gate 12.
- [Crow] Mm, the rough
sex got out of hand.
- [Tom] Ye-argh I don't
wanna be down here!
- [Crow] Wow.
Yes sir?
- Put those bags in the
back there, will yah pal?
- [Crow] The three inch taxi cab driver.
- Okay, uh where too tex?
- Police headquarters.
- Police headquarters? Are
you in some trouble sir?
- Just drive me to police headquarters
and carry this up front with you.
- Will do boss, will do boss.
- Thanks pal.
- [Cabbie] Yes sir, boss.
- [Mike] Man I can't believe I'm
being seen with Joe Don Baker.
- [Cabbie] Where do you come from Tex?
- [Geronimo] Texas.
- Oh Texas, I knew, I knew.
Do you know John Wayne?
- [Tom] Casey, yes.
- Americans, eh?
- Hey pal, you're on the
wrong side of the road.
- No, no.
- [Mike] This is the mausoleum district.
- In Malta we drive on the left.
- [Tom] There's a new convention center,
it was built in 1411.
- You from Sicily?
- (replies in a foreign language)
- Ah, Siciliano.
- [Geronimo] Hey
- Hey, hey, hey!
- [Palermo] (muttering
in a foreign language)
- Didn't I tell you not to talk to him?
- [Cabbie] (speaks in foreign language)
- Tell you what, how
about you just shuttin up
and takin me to the police station, huh?
- [Mike] Now watch this guys.
No the Maltese car! (feigns screaming)
- Ah, I do that every now and then.
- The Junkers, the Stukas
and the Messerschmitts
and they come to bombard us.
I don't know how we managed to survive.
- [Geronimo] Come on, come
on get out of here, move it!
- Pull over!
- [Crow] Ah rush hour on the 405.
(gunshot rings out and tires squeal)
- [Mike] Sorry, I'm
just tryin to pass yah!
- [Tom] Luggage hittin the
gorilla, that's different.
- [Crow] Joe Don whizzes
it in record time.
- Pull over.
- [Mike] Cars provided by Matchbox.
(tires squeal)
- [Cabbie] Please don't shoot.
- Don't worry (speaks
in a foreign language)
(Palermo shouts)
- [Tom] Let me roll on my side you jerk.
- [Crow] No you bugger!
- [Crow] Oh my butt!
(gunshot ricochets)
- [Tom] The Vatican Bank gets serious.
(automatic gun fire) (explosion)
- [Crow] Joe Don Baker's
famous delayed reaction farts.
(laughing as car tires squeal)
- [Mike] Revenge is a dish best served
with laughter and giggles.
- [Tom] And God sends a
door chassis from Heaven.
(slow country music)
- [Crow] His boots are
from Gateway computer.
- Superintendent Mifsud
would like to see you.
- [Tom] Ah, (fart noise) oh god, sorry.
- Alright.
- [Tom] Carl quit playing toll bridge.
- [Crow] Hm, you know I'm glad they went
with the frescos instead
of the drop ceiling
with the acoustical tiles.
- [Tom] Man it'd be great to put
a slip n slide in there.
- [Crow] Oh cool.
(All make wooshing noises)
- Yes.
- [Guard] Excuse me sir, you
wanted to see the American.
- Oh yes, I'll get to you later.
- [Crow] Mah-nak-um
Bey-gan transfer to Malta.
- Sorry to have arrested you, (mumbles)
you and all but you understand.
We had no way of knowing who you were.
- It's pronounced Geronimo.
- Oh yes, yes. You have
my personal apology.
- Not necessary.
- Your superior, Mr. Wilson in Washington
is on my speaker phone and
he would like to talk to you.
Please do sit down.
- [Crow] Please no Texan asses on my desk.
- Mr. Wilson, are you there?
- Yes go ahead.
- Let me apologize once
again for disturbing you
at your home at this late hour in America.
- That's perfectly alright
superintendent Mifsud.
Is Geronimo with you?
- [Mike] The big dumpling
in the weird suit?
- Yes sir, he is right here.
- You screwed it up Cowboy, what happened?
- [Tom] Well, he had a brief case.
- As near as we can tell, Palermo's people
in some way tampered with the airplane
and forced it to land before
it could get to Sicily.
- Now you listen to me Geronimo,
the Maltese and Italian
authorities will handle this from now on.
I want you to catch the next
plane back to the United States
and file your report, you understand?
- You sayin I was set up?
- That's what the man said Cowboy.
I guess you were right, I
shoulda sent one of my boys
from immigration instead of
a small town Texas sheriff.
Superintendent Mifsud, thank you
once again for your assistance
and Geronimo, you have your orders.
Thank you again superintendent, goodbye.
- Always a pleasure to
help, goodbye Mr. Wilson.
- [Crow] Good luck in your
continuing fight against Dennis.
- [Tom] Mmm rose stem salad?
- You must learn to relax, Joseph.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I have a little something
coming up, in a few weeks.
- Where?
- The far east.
- Good, I like Asian cuisine.
Besides I haven't been
there in almost a year.
- Oh, has it been that long?
- What's the hit?
- A banker.
- I'm ready.
- [Tom] Don't do that, with the robe.
- I'll get you off this
island in less than a week.
- A week?
- [Tom] A week.
- Please Don Lamanna I'll get crazy
without doing anything here.
Come on, please.
- [Tom] (mimics speech mockingly)
- [Mike] Hello sister.
- When I was your age Joseph,
I sometimes have to shake it.
(tom, mike and crow mimic
actor's speech together)
(vaults slamming)
(door whirring) (chains clinking)
(door slams) (portal shutters)
(door closes) (hatch slides shut)
- Okay hang on, check this out.
Okay, watch, see.
And there, same shot used twice.
- Continuity, unh uh.
Hey Mike come in here, you gotta see this.
- It's time to complain to Pearl.
Hey Pearl these movies you send us.
- Oh good one neldork.
What do you want I'm busy?
- Look at that, Mike's tripping Pearl.
- Yeah, again. What's his problem?
- You see sometimes Mike just trips.
- Uh huh, would you get him to stop?
- This is just one of those times.
- Oh, I see. You're complaining.
You're making the point
that once in a while
these movies leave a
little something to be
- Oh can't talk now, Mike's tripping.
- Look, I get it.
- Uh, I'll get back to
you Mike's tripping.
- Okay, fine. Now can I
- Sorry, Mike's tripping gotta go.
- I get the point. Would
you stop and let me
- What's that you say? Mike's tripping.
- Okay, I promise I will never send
another bad movie with Joe Don Baker
in which a dark haired
sheriff in a small role gets
shot and slides down a wall twice.
Okay! Happy?
- Yeah, alright.
- Well it was hard, but it was worth it.
- [Crow] Mm hmm.
- [Mike] Yeah, we'll be
right back, nice job.
- Woohoo!
- [Crow] Oh, Mike's tripping.
- [Tom] I'll say.
(upbeat keyboard music)
- [Tom] Oh, the Maltese
Macy's Thanksgiving parade.
- [Crow] The gunbelt theme.
- [Tom] I'm sure glad we get
to see Joe Don's accessories.
(knocking)
- Come on in, it's open.
- [Mike] Oh no, what's open?
- Leave it there on the table.
- Superintendent Geronimo?
- [Crow] Oh you're not ribs.
- Oh thought it was room service.
It's Geronimo, Deputy Sheriff Geronimo.
Whatchu want?
- Superintendent Mifsud sent me to see
if I can help you with anything.
- [Tom] Can you help me up?
- Only thing I really want here honey
is Palermo and I don't
think you can help me there.
- Oh I'm certain we will capture him.
He can't possibly get away.
Superintendent Mifsud will see to that.
In the meantime, since you've got the rest
of the day with nothing to
do and it's carnival time,
I thought maybe I could
show you around our island.
- [Tom] Now what'd you say after the?
- Ah thanks anyway honey.
- [Mike] Oh she has no
idea how lucky she is.
- Carnival? Is it a big carnival?
- [Crow] Can I get a balloon?
- That's what that noise is all about.
- [Mike] Someone toss me up a calzone.
- [Tom] I go east!
- [Crow] I go east!
- [Tom] I go east.
- [Crow] Oh it's the lady
Elaine Fairchild float.
- Hey you really think Palermo might still
be on this little piece
of rock you call Malta?
- Positive.
- How big is this place?
- Well the main island
is only nine miles wide
by 17 miles long.
- Well that's just big out in Texas.
- [Tom] My people, oink oink oink.
- Might be pretty hard to
hide out in a place like this.
- Think I will take a look
around and talk to some people.
Not getting anything
done in this hotel room.
- [Crow] Well not anything
you need to know about.
- [Mike] Elaine Bennis disapproves.
- [Tom] He has double
chins on his eyelids.
- [Crow] Hey the Maltese are excited,
they think he's Bum Phillips.
- [Tom] Kiss has softened their act.
- [Mike] It's goose-io the
famous Maltese children's
character, goose-io.
- [Tom] Goose-io.
- [Crow] Anything to
tide me over till lunch.
- [Mike] Eddy Rabbit's
also visiting Malta.
- [Crow] Clowns,
terrifying in any country.
- [Tom] I'll pay yah hundred dollars
for the rest of that gelato.
- [Mike] Not even walkin tall?
Come on you must've seen me in that.
- [Crow] Tammy Fay Baker!
- [Tom] Even the dead enjoy carnival.
- [Mike] Hey, John
Major goes club hopping.
- [Crow] Man the embassy in Malta rocks!
- [Tom] We're out of beef brats,
so this is the last bull shot.
- [Mike] It's the aerobics
competition on ESPN.
- [Tom] The audience is
facing the other way Debbie.
- [Mike] Both these strippers like me.
- [Crow] The one on the right
is the Miles Davis of strippers.
- [Tom] Well I guess:
♫ we better run ♫
- [Mike] Oh Kermie, take
a look at my good stuff.
- [Crow] Bobo, I didn't
know he was in this movie.
There he is.
- [Tom] The statue of
liberty after retirement.
- [Mike] Well happy saint
Europe day everybody.
- [Crow] Ah, did you dose me Mike?
Geez.
- [Mike] I wish it were a root beer float.
- Hey wait where are you
going, where'd you leave, wait.
- [Tom] Let's beat it or my huge
Maltese fan base will crush me.
- [Mike] Dennis Weaver.
- [Crow] (gasps)
A float got loose!
Oh no it's Joe Don Baker, sorry.
- [Tom] Oh I'm the star
of Mitchell, thank you.
Yeah, a bit part in Goldeneye, yep.
- [Mike] Hugo Boss and his body guards.
- Whatcha up to?
- Stay out of this.
- [Crow] You better stand up wind of me.
- Hold it! Right there.
- [Tom] Just a little to the left, good.
- Joseph Palermo, where is he?
- [Mike] Mr. Palermo, paging Mr. Palermo.
- [Crow] High goon.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Okay, that's close enough.
- [Tom] Come on, no closer please!
- [Mike] No, no, no, no
- [Crow] Hey!
- [Mike] Enzio, there's
a cowboy, oh, oh, cowboy.
- [Crow] This guy's takin
too long in the phone booth
and I gotta pee.
- [Mike] Wow, he' wearin a Chia pet hat.
- [Mike] None of them are sponge worthy.
- Think you can take me?
- [Crow] To a pizza place?
- [Tom] Giuseppe Don Baker.
- Go ahead on.
- [Mike] Could that be Hercules, hmm?
- [Tom] Blech!
- [Crow] Ew!
- [Tom, Crow, Mike] (exclaim in disgust)
- [Crow] Jackie O
- [Tom] The ugly, the ugly and the ugly.
The last thing a sausage sees.
- [Crow] (sings in a foreign language)
- [Tom] Oh please, don't fight.
(gunshot)
When fat kills fat.
- [Crow] Let me fall and turn so that
these delicious roma tomatoes
fall right into my mouth!
- [Mike] Give me my jockey back.
- Halt, wait a minute!
Don't do anything stupid with that kid.
- [Tom] Like pick up
something hot with him.
- I'll blow his brains out!
- Come on and get me, you spineless!
- Get back!
- Okay, I'm putting it away.
Come on, let's talk.
- [Tom] We're drifting apart.
- Come on, don't do anything.
- [Crow] Don't juggle or call your aunt.
(mother cries out)
- Alright.
- [Crow] Wah, wah.
- Think you can take me, go ahead on.
It's your move.
- [Tom] He saved Napoleon.
- Oh come here.
- [Tom] Oh Josephine!
- [Crow] I will fart on
your head as my revenge!
- Superintendent Mifsud
would like to see you.
- [Tom] Alright (farts, grunts, belches)
My little boats are coming through.
- [Mike] Come on, shut up Carl.
- [Crow] Heh, heh I'm wearin
spurs on your Italian marble.
(upbeat keyboard music)
- Really sir, you must listen to the story
from the beginning,
then you will understand
what really happened, please.
- Excuse me sir, you
want to see the American.
- Ah yes, yes.
Mr. Wilson from Washington
would like to speak to you.
- [Mike] The accursed
menace has struck again.
- Hi are you there Mr. Wilson?
- Damn it Geronimo, what the
hell is goin on over there?
We've had excellent relations with Malta
for over a hundred years.
You tryin to change all that?
Now what the hell's goin on?
- The situation demanded action.
What I did was appropriate.
I recognized the, that helped
Palermo get loose from me.
So I tried to arrest him.
- [Crow] Ooh Cheeseits.
- That is correct sir,
the situation was dictated
by the suspect.
- They weren't suspects.
- [Tom] Don't show me.
- Now look Cowboy, you do exactly
as superintendent Mifsud says.
Do you read me Geronimo? Exactly!
And then get your, on the
next plane back to Texas.
- [Tom] And obey lieutenant
Tiramisu, till then.
- Do you read me?
- I read you, sir.
- Superintendent Mifsud,
- [Crow] I am little!
- thank you for your
understanding and once again
let me apologize on behalf of
the United States government
for the actions of sheriff Geronimo.
- Apology accepted.
- Thank you and if I can be
of any further assistance,
please let me know.
- Yes, I will.
Let's hope we have no further
need for your assistance.
Goodbye.
- Bye.
- [Mike] He looks like Rue McClanahan.
- Where's my gun?
- Your weapon?
- [Geronimo] Yeah.
- Your weapon is staying
locked in my desk until
you leave on tomorrow's plane, understand?
- It's your country.
- Please try and remember that.
- Really sir, I must protest
Mr. Geronimo did nothing.
- That's alright honey, the
situation's all been settled.
Hasn't it superintendent Mifsud?
Look thanks for speaking
up in there for me honey,
but it really wasn't necessary.
- I didn't do it for you, I did it because
it was the truth and it's
my job to tell the truth.
- Ah great, is that what
you think the job is?
- Yeah, well partly.
- Well the way I see it,
it's the law officer's job
to get the lawbreakers off the street.
Make the street safe for the good people,
get rid of the scum.
- What about the law?
The police officer must obey that too.
- [Tom] More gravy please.
- Hey pal, you got any Malox?
- Malox? No sir.
- Then bring me a tall
glass of milk, okay?
- Glass of milk, yes sir.
- And the check.
- [Crow] Oh, and another veal head.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, look Officer Kasar.
- [Mike] Officer Hot. (purrs)
- Let me set you straight about the law.
Now of course the lawman
must obey the law.
- [Mike] (grunts)
- The law must be just.
Now there's lots of bad
people out there using the law
for their own things.
- [Tom] (belches)
- Well some of us gotta
stand up for justice.
- Seems awful simple to me.
- It is, till the politicians,
the lawyers get involved.
You know how they are.
- Your milk sir.
- Thank you, appreciate it.
- [Tom] Mmm barium. (gulping noises)
- [Crow] His arteries are
just lookin at each other
shaking their heads.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- Yeah sure, I'm fine, thank you.
- [Tom] (belches)
- Well, well I did get shot
up a few years ago in Dallas
and sometimes it acts up a bit.
- Maybe you're not used to Maltese food.
- No, no the food's good.
Sure is a lot of it too.
- [Mike] That fits right in with my plan.
- Ah hey, how much is
that in American money?
- On the Maltese police department.
- Oh, well thank you little lady.
- [Crow] You're welcome huge man.
- Momma taught me never
to pass up a free meal.
As you can tell.
- [Tom] Ah boy up with
people it sure changed.
- [Mike] I did that before I had kids.
- [Crow] Brought to you by
the triangle foundation.
- [Mike] What are they, cowboys, pirates,
hardware store clerks?
- [Tom] Ew Valerie one
of the guppies is dead!
- What can I get you?
- Manhattan on the rocks.
- We don't have mixed drinks.
Beer, wine or straight liquor only.
- Would you believe that?
- [Mike] Do you have Sprite?
- Straight bourbon, okay? Straight.
- [Tom] Really had his heart
set on a Ramos Gin Fizz.
- [Crow] The Indigo Girls early days.
- Don Lamanna I am honored,
what can I get you?
- Nothing, thank you.
- [Mike] There's still
a million Lira cover.
- Get the word to that
cowboy that I am at this bar.
We will be waiting for him, okay?
- [Crow] (mocking gibberish)
- [Tom] Hey you can come
in the dressing room,
tell me how these pants fit?
- [Geronimo] You have a fat limit or what?
- [Maria] My instructions are
to show you around our island.
- [Geronimo] Well I'm not here
as a damn tourist, I'm here
to get Palermo.
- [Crow] (smooches air)
- [Geronimo] Where do
they keep the broads?
- [Maria] How do you mean?
- [Geronimo] Hookers,
hustlers, prostitutes?
- [Crow] I heard that!
- Well years ago when sailors used to come
to our island there was a place
called the gut, but now...
- [Geronimo] That'll
be it, which way is it?
- [Tom] We don't accept coupons.
- [Crow] I'm gonna put on
hot pants and go under cover.
- You want a pig like Palermo?
You go to the pig stye where he wallows.
- [Mike] Well you'd know pigs.
- [Geronimo] Hi there kid.
- [Tom] It is the Bufford puss.
- Excuse me.
- [Crow] Not for any price.
- I hate to interrupt your
business, but I'm looking
for this Italian guy named Joe Palermo.
He's about six feet tall a 180
pounds, real sharp dresser.
I wonder if you could help me find him?
- [Mike] For a Werther's.
- Take American money?
- [Prostitute] Yeah all currencies.
- [Geronimo] Well look,
I'm on an expense account,
so $20 bucks is gonna have to do, huh?
- Well, you'll find him
in smuggler's tavern.
It's two blocks up from
here and then go left again.
- You know this place?
Alright, thank you honey.
You better not be lyin to me.
- No.
- [Tom] Good luck, peddle lots of sex!
- [Crow] Why am I not
getting any business?
What am I doing wrong?
- [Mike] Thanks Cher, Rhea Perlman.
- [Crow] He's hanging around lookin
for some black market Propecia.
- [Tom] Hey Crow, you've got a golden ash.
- [Crow] Shutup.
- [Mike] Boy they really
spelled Sony wrong.
- [Crow] He's guarding Malta's only plant.
- [Tom] Well see with your beef
ribs, you get a little more
meat, whereas your pork ribs
offer a higher fat content.
- [Crow] Cheap crap! Get
your cheap crap here!
- [Mike] John Rhys-Davies for sale.
- [Crow] Enjoy my fuzzy puckered midriff.
- [Tom] Mine too!
- [Mike] Mine too!
- [Tom] Oh my tummy hurts, ooh!
- [Crow] See you in your
nightmares! (cackles)
- What's the matter?
- We're being set up, there's
a guy on the balcony up there.
It's an ambush. There's
two more, Palermo's men.
- [Mike] I will sell no one.
- You watch my back.
- [Tom] Watch it jiggle as I move.
- [Crow] My first fat layer!
- [Tom] I'm allergic to vermiculite.
- [Crow] My operation game!
- [Crow] The spinners are getting away.
- [Maria] Watch out!
- [Mike] Ah, now what was that for?
- [Crow] I'm telling the mob!
Mob he's shooting at me!
- [Tom] Remind me to buy
something cute for Mr. Wilson.
- [Mike] Stop or we'll surrender!
- Hold it right there
sheriff! Maria, Maria!
- [Crow] Do you realize
you're with Joe Don Baker?
- I want every police officer
in Malta to get this order.
Arrest sheriff Geronimo on
sight, he is armed and dangerous.
Use what precaution is necessary.
- Yes sir.
- [Tom] The streets of San Fran Malta.
(gunshot ricochets)
- [Mike] Ah-noon ah-noo
- [Crow] His weight is
forcing him down the stairs.
(gunshot ricochets)
- [Tom] Oh, it was the gun's fault.
(tom beat boxing)
- [Mike] Meatloaf, Texas Ranger.
- [Crow] (sings gibberish)
(upbeat piano music)
♫ Goose-E-O, Goose-E-O, Goose-E-O,
♫ did you know I'm Goose-E-O?
♫ Friend to Maltese
children everywhere-E-O.
♫ Goose-E-O, Goose-E-O,
Goose-E-O, I bet you knew-sio.
- Oh I get it he's
Goose-E-O, hmph, adorable.
- Yeah friend to Maltese
children everywhere E-O.
- Yep, Goose-E-O, like in the movie.
- Yep, yep, yep.
- [Tom] Goose-E-O
- This must be the offal of
the sick and perverted mind of
- [Tom And Crow] Mike Nelson!
- [Tom] Yep, yep, yep.
♫ Goose-E-O ♫
(Goose-E-O cackles)
- God I hate cute!
- Well Crow, only one thing to do.
- Yep. Get him!
- [Tom] Come here you little pip squeak!
- Ooh why you hurt Goose-E-O?
- [Tom] Goose-E-O cooked!
- [Crow] Gonna make some pate outta you!
- [Tom] Yeah, there you go.
- [Tom] You're Fois Gras now buddy.
(both laughing)
- [Goose-E-O] Help me.
(gurgling and squeaking)
- Ooh, look at him go.
(cackling)
- Hey guys, what's goin.
What happened? (feigns screaming)
- Ah come on Nelson it's your
annoying gob of paper mache,
which you so ingratiatingly
called Goose-E-O.
- No this, this is Goose-E-O
the beloved folk hero
and TV star of Malta.
(crow gasps)
- Goose-E-O was sent up here
as a good will ambassador.
He teaches children lessons about love
and sharing and hygiene
and you, you killed him.
- [Tom] Uh-oh.
- [Crow] Wow, sorry Mike.
- [Tom] Yeah, and uh,
sorry Malta. (laughs)
- [Crow] I mean we try
to destroy only things
that are specifically yours.
(alarm buzzer)
- [Mike] Movie seeing time,
- [Crow] Goose-E-O!
[Tom] Sorry Goose-E-O!
(doors sliding open) (insect skittering)
(metal grinding) (wood
thudding, chains rattling)
(motors whirring)
(beeping and locks
clanking) (hinges groaning)
- [Crow] Come on.
- [Tom] Just don't tell Malta, okay?
- [Mike] Goose-E-O, poor Goose-E-O.
- [Mike] Gotta get to
my shift as alter boy.
- It's a church.
- [Crow] Whoa ah he ho, oh-uh.
- [Tom] Forget Goose-E-O.
- [Mike] Sorry.
- [Geronimo] Woman cops.
- [Tom] Check it out, looks like god's
doing alright for himself.
- [Crow] Sh-yeah
- [Mike] Dearly beloved,
we are here to get through
this thing called life, life.
- [Tom] (beat boxing)
- [Crow] (beat boxing)
Oh great there's announcements.
- [Tom] Mmm, new arch-bishop's cute.
- [Mike] I hear the
hosts are delicious here.
- You see him?
- No I don't know where he went.
- [Crow] Uh-oh he ascended into heaven.
- Take a look around.
- [Tom] Uh, you know, go ahead on.
- [Crow] Hey you know
the problem with churches
is they wear their
religion on their sleeves.
I mean I go into a church, I don't wanna
be assaulted with god,
god, god all the time.
- [Mike] I gotta bundle
up before I wack that guy.
- [Tom] Lord please make my
hair a tangled grey mass.
Thank you.
- [Crow] I'm just going to read
from the Robert James Waller book today.
- [Mike] The homily was directed
at me last week, wasn't it?
- [Tom] Oh hi, mare!
- [Mike] Uh, dominoes pizza
delivers, I don't know.
- [Crow] Please let me
kill a lot of people.
- [Mike] Wow, apparently the Malta Vikings
are playing today.
- [Tom] Everybody's going off to
those big mega-cathedrals
in the suburbs now.
- Father, father, father
I want to confess!
- I can't.
- But please father, I want to confess.
- Well, please.
- [Crow] God is dead, we're closed.
- [Mike] I overcooked my brezz-ules.
- Okay father I am a very good woman.
- Yes, yes, don't worry.
- [Tom] He needs more (speaks
in a foreign language)
- Yes, don't worry, anything
you want, anything you say.
- What do you think I watched?
- [Tom] Anything you say?
- [Mike] (chuckles)
- Don't worry sister.
- [Tom] Whatever.
- Sister, please, please just relax.
- [Mike] I'm gonna light a
candle to Saint Tom Landry.
- [Tom] And then I shot him 30 times.
- We gotta look behind these side doors.
We need a priest, are they locked or what?
- No they won't be locked.
- [Crow] Look just stop sinning, alright.
- Father, I remember something.
I have more sins to confess.
- Hold it there pal.
Hey, wait a minute!
- [Mike] Guess he's a felonious monk.
- [Tom] Oh!
- [Crow] Man!
- [Tom] Please have hosts at Wal-Greens,
please have hosts at Wal-Greens!
♫ He's a beef town chunk
on a Saturday night ♫
(dramatic electric guitar and synth drums)
- [Mark] Bill's Harbor.
- [Tom] Hey and there's the Malta Navy.
That's it. All of it.
- [Crow] Hello Major Tom,
hello there Major Tom.
How's it goin Tom?
(chuckling)
- [Mike] God I hate running
in a long dress and heels.
- [Tom] I'm gonna nail
some feces to his head.
- [Mike] So sad the operation petty-coat
set sitting out there rusting.
- [Crow] (sighs)
You'll have to grease me
and push me through here.
- [Tom] Good props in this movie.
- [Mike] I had to chase a monk once.
Sold me a bunch of moldy
bread, the son of a.
- Alright look, I'm out of bullets.
I'm gonna run a bluff on him.
- [Tom] God, god!
There's a guy chasing me!
- [Mike] The Franciscan 10k race!
- [Crow] Yeah the winner gets to
relinquish more of his worldly goods.
- [Tom] Look they're
goin by a house of blues.
- [Tom] You son of a!
- [Crow] You're the son of a!
(tense chase music)
- [Tom] (beat boxing)
- [Mike] Yes every exciting
angstrom of their chase
will be shown.
- [Tom] (imitating mocking guitars chords)
This is papal bow man. (imitating guitar)
- [Crow] Oh, I gotta quit
puttin off that by-pass surgery.
- [Maria] Wait hold on.
- Why we're both out of bullets.
- [Mike] I'm gonna look up his dress.
- [Tom] Yes, asses
splashed across the screen.
- [Crow] Thank you.
- [Tom] I'm scared of heights
where there's no food.
- [Geronimo] Maria!
- [Tom] Ble-Ow!
- [Geronimo] Do you see him?
- No I don't know where he is.
- Well keep looking!
- [Tom] I'm gonna lay down for a while.
- [Mike] Ah he was down jiggin
with the losers in steerage.
(suspenseful violin music)
- [Tom] (imitating violin chords)
Ooh, right in the lunch.
- [Crow] Like punching
a bag of Irish oatmeal.
- [Tom] (beat boxing)
- [Mike] He's battling the
ghost of Christmas future.
- [Tom] He screwed me on the
royalties to that chant album.
- [Crow] I'll flagellate
myself, thank you.
- [Tom] Oh thank you
for savin me tiny woman.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] (tom beat boxing)
Damn it I forgot about vespers!
- [Crow] I'm gonna go
catch some monk fish!
- [Tom] (beat boxing)
- [Crow] Oh I remember
this episode of super monk.
Super monk went bad for a
while, but then he got better.
- [Tom] Damn boat load limits
I'm always exceeding them.
- [Crow] I'm takin on water!
Oh that's just me sweatin.
- [Mike] There's a bunch
of armed nuns on jet skis
out there waitin for him.
- [Tom] (grunting in mock pain)
- [Crow] My robe does wick away moisture!
- [Mike] He's leavin a frangelico slick.
(laughing)
- [Tom] (beat boxing)
Hi lost city of the Incas.
- [Crow] (grunting in mock pain)
- [Mike] Now there's Thomas Merton
piloting, this Budweiser.
- [Crow] (imitating crowd cheering)
- [Tom] This was all to
get a shot of the Pacnorse.
- [Crow] Yeah.
Ah, this movie's really drawing me in.
To a deep well of despair.
- [Tom] (beat boxing)
- [Mike] Oh man, this isn't gonna end
until they round Cape Horn, is it?
- [Tom] (imitating chase music)
Oh you're looking for me?
- [Crow] Why don't men want to
join the priesthood anymore?
It looks like a blast to me.
- [Tom] It's dangerous for
Joe Don to be in the water.
Someone's bound to harpoon him.
- [Tom] Oh big gas bubble!
Ah the Holy See promised air support,
but never came through.
- [Crow] This is how the
crusades were fought too, right?
- [Mike] Yeah.
- [Crow] It's a dam!
- [Mike] You know at any time Joe Don
could lay down a torpedo, I know that.
- [Tom] (chortles)
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Tom] Ah yes and now back
to the beginning of the chase.
- [Mike] Yay.
- [Crow] Ah, where's the
perfect storm when you need it?
- [Mike] Wow, that's
not a sexual metaphor.
- [Tom] It's illegal to net monks.
- [Mike] (laughs)
- [Crow] You know nets are
overrated weapons.
- [Mike] Yeah throw a danish at him,
that would work better.
- [Tom] Yes and after all that,
our hero is down with one punch.
- [Crow] Nice try Joe Don!
I am off to make Xerox commercials!
- [Tom And Crow] (beat boxing
and mocking chase music)
- You have failed.
- No, no, not yet. I'll
get this, I swear it.
- [Mike] I love these guys.
- We have done many jobs,
- [Crow] They're awesome.
- Many times over the
years, you are the best.
- [Mike] Fallin for you?
- The best because you had
no feeling, no emotion.
But now you are trying
- [Palermo] He killed Tony.
This is special.
- You've had your chance.
- [Mike] (sputtering gibberish)
- Give me 24 hours, I'll
kill him I swear it.
- I am afraid not Joseph.
- [Tom] We are going to
Euro-Disney tomorrow.
- I am bringing somebody from Rome.
- [Mike] This is going to
end in a kiss isn't it?
- Don Lamanna please, the
hit in the Far East is a gift
to you for the American, give me 24 hours
that's all I ask you.
- [Crow] No you have one day!
- 24 hours. Him or you.
- Officer Kassa told me what happened.
I guess it couldn't be helped
- [Mike] Akimbo vision.
- [Mifsud] but you are a
working disaster area sheriff.
The last violence that happened in Malta
was some kids blowing up
the toilets at the airport.
You come to our country and
there are bodies in the street.
- [Tom] And furthermore (yells gibberish)
- You use our country like your
own private shooting range.
I realize that your name is
that of a great American Indian
warrior, but this violence must stop.
- Well I couldn't agree with yah more.
Palermo's men started shootin
at me, I had to defend myself.
- Yes yes I see what you mean.
- [Mike] I cave in.
- Look I still think I can help you guys.
I mean I tracked him in
Texas, I chased him all over
this island of yours.
I know him, I know how he thinks.
I can get that.
- (speaks in a foreign language)
- [Tom] Geronimo!
- If there is one more
- [Mike] Get back up.
- [Mifsud] incident, just one more.
- [Tom] Just a joke.
- Chose by you are not, as god as my judge
I will keep you in custody until
your plane leaves tomorrow.
- [Mike] There a meal?
- [Mifsud] Your word as an
American police officer that you
will cause no more problems.
- As an American police officer?
- Yes!
- [Crow] A giant baby in a hat.
- You got my word.
- [Mike] Uh there was no buffet in there.
What the hell's the deal?
- Your boss is wrong Maria,
this ain't gonna stop.
Look that, killed my partner;
I killed his brother.
Ain't no way this is gonna end up
with both of us walkin around.
- But you gave your word
to superintendent Mifsud.
- I gave my word as an
American police officer.
Hell I'm a Texas lawman.
- [Tom] Doh.
- Please don't do anything
else, superintendent Mifsud
is sure to put you away
this time, believe me.
- I believe you but
that ain't the problem.
The problem is I gotta find
Palermo before he finds me.
- [Tom] Take your pig mask off.
- The only lead we got's that honky tonk
called Smuggler's Tavern
where he set me up.
I'm gonna go talk them good ole boys.
- [Crow] Smuggler's
Tavern we have strippers
and skillet breakfasts.
- [Mike] You know I prefer
the Embezzler's Tavern.
- [Tom] It's Joe Don Baker, huh.
(lively guitar and drums)
- [Tom] A shaved bear!
- [Bartender] What will it be Tex?
- Got any Malox?
- [Bartender] Malox,
what the hell is that?
- Just give me a tall glass of milk.
- Milk!
(laughter)
Hey we got a real American Cowboy here!
- Sorry Tex, no milk.
- Well maybe you can help me, I'm lookin
for this Italian guy
- [Tom] Oof
- [Geronimo] named Joe Palermo.
- [Mike] Oh that's him dancing.
- Around six feet tall, a 180 pounds.
- [Crow] Breasts a
little bigger than hers.
- Nice dresser.
- I just serve drinks, I don't
pay attention who drinks them.
- I wouldn't like it if I
found out you's lyin to me.
- [Tom] Well you're fat.
- I know a lot of Italians.
- I'm talkin to this man here, you just
mind your business and drink your beer.
- You don't like beer, Tex?
He likes milk! (laughs)
Here have some of my beer.
- [Tom] It's a bar full
of Stuart Margolises.
- [Mike] Oh Don what are
you, oh it's the beer.
- [Crow] It don't matter,
I had em beer proofed.
- Tell you what, why don't
you just get down there
and clean them boots?
Then we'll talk about Italians.
- [Tom] Did I mention he likes milk?
- Now hold it, hold it, just a minute.
- [Crow] Let's go corral horses.
- I don't want any trouble here!
- [Tom] Get the milk lover!
- Stop this fighting!
- [Tom] Well I did all I could.
- What's the matter with you guys?
- [Crow] You don't want Joe Don
throwing a stool at you, ooh.
- [Tom] Uh okay, I'll wait.
- [Crow] Look out men
he has an inner-tube!
- [Tom] Things!
- [Mike] He's winning, but
these guys are Maltese.
- [Tom] Yeah, there's that.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Crow] He's battling
a Red Hot Chilli Pepper!
- [Tom] Sweep!
- [Tom] Ah the hall monitors are here.
- Yeah, I know.
- [Tom] Yeah, oh god. (fart noises)
- Superintendent Mifsud wants
to see me, I know the way.
- [Crow] Ding, ding, bridge up!
- [Mike] Stop it Carl!
- [Mike] (grunts in disgust)
- [Tom] Let's watch
him Q-tip his ears now.
- Excuse me sir, the American.
- Oh, it has been a long day sheriff.
- [Crow] Yes it has.
- We in Malta will tell stories of you
to our great grandchildren.
- Wait a minute, I
didn't start that ruckus.
- Ruckus? That's what you call it?
- [Mike] I prefer fracas.
- My superiors feel that you should be
locked up for a very long time.
How do you feel about that?
- I wouldn't like it sir.
- No I suppose you wouldn't,
our jails are not as
comfortable as yours in America are they?
- Well actually I wish ours
were a lot more like yours.
- Flattery will not help
your situation here sheriff.
- [Crow] Geronimo.
- Actually I am to blame.
If officer Maria Kassa had been with you,
this would not have happened.
I guess she was not ready
for this assignment.
- Wait a minute, it wasn't her fault.
She didn't have a thing to do with this!
- Oh don't trouble yourself
officer kassa has been relieved
of further responsibility
regarding your case.
- You mean she's been reassigned?
- That is correct.
- Well it's your business,
but let me tell you
she's one hell of a fine officer.
- Thank you.
- Say, how about you give me about
10 minutes with that bartender?
Now I can get the information out of him.
- I'm not sure you understand
the position here sheriff.
- [Mike] Yeah.
- My superiors have
instructed me in clear terms
you are no longer involved with this case.
I have personally questioned the bartender
and he has no knowledge of Mr. Palermo.
- Yeah, well let me talk to
him I can get the information
- Your plane leaves in less than 10 hours.
- [Mike] Yeah.
- And I suggest you stay in your hotel
and you will be escorted
to the airport tomorrow.
- I'm under house arrest?
- You could stay in
your cell if you prefer.
- Hey cut me some slack.
- (yells in foreign language)
- [Tom] You have fleshy wrists.
- The choice is yours,
the hotel or your cell.
- Well hotel, but, hey pal come
here I want to talk to you!
Wait a minute, listen!
(country guitar riff)
- [Crow] Day seven of his shirt.
- Say pal, tell me somethin, about Malta.
Was there really a falcon?
- Well yes as a matter of fact there was.
(grunts in pain)
- You okay?
- It's an old wound.
- [Mike] Heart attack, it's
the only exercise he ever gets.
- Hey, hey!
- [Tom] Ooh, mmm.
- [Crow] Hey.
- I work to do pal, I'm sorry about this.
- [Tom] I hate it when you throw a fight
and nobody stays to help yah clean up.
- Go away we're closed.
- [Crow] Ooh we're not closed for you.
- I don't want any more trouble.
- Well that's exactly
what you're gonna get
unless I get some answers
about that Ih-tally.
Now look at that.
You know my ancestors.
- [Mike] Were large, soft rocks.
- They used to skin their enemies.
Just peel the skin right off the bone.
- [Crow] Well the trick was to get it all
in one peel like this.
- Take a sharp knife and just
cut layer after layer of flesh.
Real experts, the Apaches.
You've heard of the Apaches haven't you?
- [Mike] The cabbage patchies?
- [Geronimo] So maybe you want
- [Crow And Tom] Whoa.
- [Geronimo] to tell me where
I can find this Joe Palermo?
- [Crow] White pain.
- [Geronimo] Maybe before I
show you more about how to
skin somebody.
- [Mike] Felonious Monk.
- Alright, I know this
Italian guy who's been messing
with one of my dancers, that's all.
- Where is she?
- In there, in the dressing room.
- Better not be lyin to me.
(knife thunking into wood)
- [Tom] Or you won't have an
unpeeled orange in the place.
- [Crow] I'd better call my mother,
she can defend me from this big man.
(upbeat keyboard music)
- I told you.
- [Tom] We're not hiring.
- I don't know what you are talking about.
- I think you do, if I
can just make you realize
that you're better off telling
me what I want to know.
- [Crow] Hmm.
- Than not tellin me what I want to know,
then you're gonna tell
me what I want to know.
- [Crow] Where do you go
for prime rib in this town?
- But I don't need this trouble.
Why you can't speak of
something else, huh?
- What you don't need is trouble from me.
That I-Tally is a pussy
cat compared to me.
- [Tom] Our hero, a murderous
oaf who threatens women
with coat hangers.
- Look, but
- [Crow] Thank you, I will.
- I am a dead lady if
I'm here seen with you.
- I'll protect you.
- [Mike] You can hide in my hat.
- I hear you are looking for me.
- You're gonna have some fun Cowboy.
- [Crow] Well usually the doctor
just jabs my vast white buttocks.
- [Tom] I think it was juiced vegetables,
he just can't handle it.
- Come on Cowboy, fight. (laughs)
- [Mike] Now let's look at this.
- [Crow] Ah here's where
I left my ice cream cone.
- [Tom] Guess where this is going Joe Don.
- [Mike] Now put your hand
in this bowl of eyeballs.
(tom and crow gasp)
(grunting)
- [Tom] Fire bad. (grunts)
- [Crow] Joe Don Baker is
carried to set of Final Justice.
- [Tom] (grunts, belches and farts)
- [Crow] They're going to
grandpa's laboratory, Oy-Man.
- [Mike] See that's the
candle they have to light
when Joe Don uses the bathroom.
- [Crow] We'll see what Count
Chocula has to say about this.
- [Geronimo] Wait a minute!
- You're ours, remember it cowboy.
I'm gonna make your death real slow.
- [Mike] Uh because I'm drunk.
- You're gonna pay for my brother.
You're gonna pay for him and
I'm gonna have a lot of fun.
- [Tom] This is good
expectations management.
- [Crow] Joe Don, we're
not, we're not done
with the scene, Joe
Don! (grunts resignedly)
- [Tom] Oh I'm glad we
skipped the cavity search.
- Don Lamanna did you want to see me?
- Yeah sit down.
- [Mike] Oh he's been invited to panel.
- It was not wise to
bring the American here.
- He'll be dead in 24
hours just like I promised.
- Then kill him and be done with it.
- [Crow] Run him over with your Vespa!
- A quick death is too easy.
I want to make it slow for him.
- Just see to it Mr.
Geronimo is dead by tomorrow.
- [Tom] Geronimo!
- You have my word.
- [Crow] There he goes again.
- I'm aware of that Joseph.
(incoherent muttering)
- [Tom] What the hell?
- [Mike] Drunk again?
- [Crow] Well I got the midnight
to eight strip shift, so.
- [Tom] And I left a load
of triangles in the dryer.
- [Crow] Take me away Pen-Wah.
- [Mike] I guess I better study
for my stripper's board exams.
- [Crow] Why did she wear
her prom dress to bed?
- [Tom] Christian Slater's
gonna fly tomorrow,
I better get this back to him.
- [Crow] Hm, I sense cheeseburgers.
- [Tom] Lap dance home delivery.
- You said you'd protect
me, did you mean it?
- I know Palermo, I won't
underestimate him again.
You've got my word.
- Okay.
- [Mike] You know I really don't care
for this remake of a lion in winter.
- [Crow] Torch holders are
an option on newer homes.
- [Mike] I should let you
know I ate the mattress
in my cell, you might wanna replace that.
- [Crow] Change into one of my nightgowns
and disguise yourself as me.
- [Tom] Usually I have nightvision goggles
for raidin the fridge, but I
forgot to bring em with me.
- [Mike] Uh please don't
use the guest towels
for toilet paper like you
did last time, thank you.
(lock clanking, door slamming)
(beeping and motor whirring)
(chain clinking and wood door slamming)
(metal squealing and door dragging)
(hatch sliding and clicking)
- Ah thank you for coming,
I am ready to present
my report on Malta, ahem.
Malta a nation and a country.
Malta is a small archipelago
in the Mediterranean sea near Sicily.
The knights of Saint John
founded Malta in the middle ages.
Industries are ship building,
manufacturing and tourism.
- [Tom] Oh, that's nice.
- Thank you Crow that
was very informative.
- Well that's all the hard
data, now on to the good stuff.
It's interesting to note
that the countries population
of 350,000 contains more women than men.
Especially since the men are
so womany in the first place.
- Uh Crow?
- Hang on Mike.
It's no wonder Malta is one
of the most conquered islands
in history, what with the
Maltese men who consistently
wet themselves
- [Tom] Whoa!
- [Crow] and surrender
at the sight of anyone
remotely bigger than them.
- Now this is interesting!
- [Crow] You bet.
This population of so-called men is known
throughout the world as a
gaggle of flaccid ninnys
whose delicate fingers
can barely hold up their
stinky Maltese cigarettes.
- (laughing) Crow what are you saying?
- Wait it gets better.
- [Tom] Oh boy.
- [Crow] Famous for breath
so bad it could melt steel,
- [Tom] Wow.
- [Crow] these greasy
goat-loving mommas boys
are known in the European
community for having the tiniest,
most shriveled up
- [Mike] Okay Crow,
alright stop, please come one!
- [Crow] What, Mike? Come on.
Don't tell me you're gonna defend
these witless, tight-shirted
clowns of walking B-O.
- Okay, listen stop it, okay?
There must be something wrong with yah,
let me take a look at you.
- [Crow] What, what?
- [Tom] Well since when have you had
this seething hatred of Maltese men?
- Well ever since I was
a little boy, Servo.
Some forgotten Maltese
horror deeply wounded
my tender young psyche.
- Uh you were never a little boy Crow.
You were built in space.
- Well that's pretty traumatic.
Maybe I was built by some
sweaty, tiny batch Maltese
capitulator who
- [Mike] Okay, stop it now.
I think I found the problem.
I think there's a tiny flaw
in the coding substructure
of the risk processor.
- [Tom] There it is.
- [Crow] No doubt put there by a lisping,
cheese gorging Maltese eunuch.
- No, alright I'll just uh, swap this out
and you should be right as rain, okay?
Alright there we go.
There now, Crow.
What do you think about Maltese men?
- Who? Maltese men?
I don't know I never really met one.
- [Tom] Whew, good.
- [Mike] Oh good, there we go,
back to normal.
- Oh Maltese men, well let
me tell you about those
puking, hairy-necked freaks!
- [Tom] Grab him!
- [Mike] (shushing)
- [Crow] I just
- [Mike] Let me just, stop.
Let me just.
(synthesized organ music)
(mike sighs)
- [Crow] Don't worry I'll
subdue him by layin on him.
- [Mike] If I die, I wanna be
buried next to the Sizzler.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] He became a pillow!
(woman groaning in pain)
- [Crow] Your personal funk
is getting to me. (grunts)
- [Tom] I fell on my smuckers.
- [Crow] Well to be fair, he never said
he'd protect her neck.
- [Mike] Wow they have a
strict early checkout policy.
(tense music)
♫ out here in the fields ♫
- [Crow] Bum, bum.
(man screams)
- [Crow] Boom, bum, bum.
- You got nowhere to go!
She got what she deserved.
Come inside,
- [Crow] Tony.
- [Palermo] I'm going
to make it easy on you.
That little injection I gave
you wasn't so bad now, was it?
Maybe you'd like a little more huh?
- [Tom] (grunts, groans and farts)
Geronimo, I mean me!
- [Mike] Ha, ha.
- [Crow] Finally paid off.
- There he is, get him!
- [Mike] Oh right, like his shins wouldn't
be protruding through his
stomach after that jump.
- He's heading to the boat, let's go!
- [Crow] Son of a beep.
- [Crow] I'm glad that's
a nudey suit in name only.
- [Mike] Thank you.
- [Crow] Oh no, I think
I'll need a freighter.
- [Mike] Right now the screen
writers are asking themselves,
have we had a boat chase yet?
- [Tom] Uh, no I don't think so.
- [Crow] Well should we look back
at what we've written just to make sure?
- [Tom] I think we'd
remember if we had done that.
- [Crow] Well if we haven't done one,
we should put one in.
People love em.
- [Tom] Mm hmm.
- [Mike] Yep, that's what
the screen writers are sayin.
- [Crow] Screen writers are sayin it.
- [Tom] That was close!
- Get this tub movin, come on!
- [Crow] Darn it!
The movie Midway had
fewer boats than this.
(automatic gunfire)
- [Tom] Ah he finally exploded.
- [Mike] Packers!
- I killed the, back to land!
- [Mike] (laughs)
- [Tom] Yes I killed
(grunting mocking gibberish)
- [Mike] I guess.
- [Crow] Don't worry, his
heart will go ahead on.
- I don't see him.
- [Mike] There's an elephant
seal, oh that's him.
- He lives with the fishes.
- [Tom] Although they're
actually tryin to kick him out.
- Goodbye Cowboy.
- [Crow] Meanwhile there's
tsunamis slamming into Italy.
- This time I am sure, is dead, I got him.
- Where is the body?
- At the bottom of the Mediterranean.
- How can you be so certain?
- Don Lamanna we were
several miles at sea.
The explosion alone would kill anyone.
- [Mike] Let's get out of this jukebox.
- [Lamanna] The American has
proven he is not just anyone.
Well let's hope that this is done.
- [Crow] You're welcome, jeez.
- [Tom] Every shark in the ocean
and they still can't finish him.
- He has been missing for
- [Crow] (phlegm noises)
- [Mifsud] five days Mr. Wilson.
We have combed the island for him.
If this man Palermo got him,
I'm afraid he must be dead.
Probably buried somewhere far out at sea.
We'll never find his body.
- I don't think so sir.
- What makes you say that?
- I'm just not convinced
that sheriff Geronimo's dead.
- [Mike] Well I'm Dick Cabbot.
- Me too sir, that Indian's still alive.
- [Crow] Hey shut up!
- I feel it.
- [Tom] Huh, two fully dressed silkies.
(accordion music)
- [Crow] Hey Malta! Get a tree!
- [Tom] Sadly his arm was still in there.
- [Mike] Hey is my dry cleaning done yet?
- [Crow] Here it is liquid beef.
(grunts)
- [Tom] Could I have my Nuk?
- [Crow] (gulping noise)
- [Mike] I hope they're hiring
triangle-butted dancers.
- Excuse me.
- No listen, I've already
told you all I know.
- Just one last time, okay?
Are you sure the American
didn't come back here
after the fight?
- That's right and I've got some damages,
which somebody must pay for.
- Hey!
- [Crow] I am from Malta!
- [Patron] If you see
that Cowboy, tell him
I'm lookin for him too.
- Excuse me sir, you
wanted my final report
on sheriff Geronimo?
- Yes I do.
- Well I still can't
believe it but nobody's seen
or heard from him on the whole island.
- [Tom] We're doing our bridal registry.
- Well I can't stay here any longer,
I gotta get back to the states.
I'll be leaving tomorrow,
as far as I'm concerned
Thomas Jefferson Geronimo
the third is dead.
- [Mike] Mmm sun-dried cans.
- You nearly hit it, a
little more practice.
Pull it back hard.
- [Crow] But I am a Maltese male! Sorry.
- Let me try.
- [Mike] They're saving rocks in case
there's a rock shortage.
- I used to hunt squirrels
and jackrabbits back in Texas.
That's how we ate.
- [Tom] We stuffed dead, raw
squirrels into our mouths.
- [Crow] Wait I blacked your hat!
- [Mike] Well they hustled him out
of the village pretty quickly.
- [Tom] But wait, I'm
still sick and wounded.
- [Crow] Uh huh, good bye!
- Good bye, thanks a million!
- [Tom] That's thanks a
ten with the exchange rate.
- [Crow] Oh dear.
♫ Everybody's burpin at me, I can't
♫ smell a thing they're eatin ♫
- [Crow] He makes Randy Quaid
look subtle and diminutive.
- [Mike] Excuse me, Joe
Don Baker comin through.
- Appreciate it.
- Just because you won't
be here, it's okay.
I want you to know that
I'll find him for you.
- [Mike] Mmm alfredo sauce.
- Well hell, for all we know
he's already off this island.
- Oh no I don't think.
Our security and customs are very strict.
- Well what if he takes a boat.
- We have patrol boats around the island.
- Well if you think he's still here,
I've got a couple hours
before my plane leaves.
There's a man I want to talk to.
- Now wait a minute,
you're under strict orders
from superintendent Mifsud
not to cause any trouble.
I've personally guaranteed your behavior.
- [Crow] Established.
- I'm not gonna misbehave.
I just wanna ask this bartender
a few little ole questions.
Are you still sayin you had nothin
to do with Palermo showin up here?
(water splashing and gagging)
- [Crow] (gagging and spitting)
- I told you, I swear.
I just met Italian guy
- [Tom] It's a classic (mutters)
- [Mike] (chuckles)
- [Geronimo] Well I'm not convinced.
I don't believe Palermo
just happened to show up.
- [Crow] You're getting
Vitalis on the turtles.
- I didn't tell him.
- Look I promised that
little girl I'd protect her.
I didn't make good on that promise.
- [Mike] Where'd he go, K-K-K-Ken?
- [Geronimo] Where is he!
- [Bartender] I don't know!
- [Geronimo] Where is that bastard?
- Take it easy sheriff.
I understand your frustration.
- [Tom] I don't understand
how you got a movie role.
- Sheriff this is not the wild west.
We have laws here, you will
spend the night incarcerated.
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Mifsud] And I will
personally escort you
to the airport tomorrow morning.
- [Crow] But mah butt doubles as muh face!
- I'm sorry I was just following orders.
- Yeah, I understand orders.
You know there's an old saying.
You know you're right, go ahead
on, cause right makes might.
Now that, there knows where Palermo is
and I could've got it out of him.
Can you Maria?
- [Tom] You've given me
a lot to think about.
Like how can one man be that sweaty?
- [Mike] Ah, we're stuck in
a mobius strip of a movie.
- [Crow] Save us.
(indistinct voices)
- I have the orders
right here in my purse.
Now let me see the prisoner.
I'm awful nervous with this thing,
so don't do anything foolish,
just open up the cell.
Hurry up, quick, open up!
- [Crow] I'm a Maltese man, I surrender.
Sorry.
- [Geronimo] Get in there.
- [Mike] (chuckles) We'll work on it.
- [Crow] Yeah thanks.
- [Maria] No I don't think so.
Here I got your gun.
- [Geronimo] Good girl.
- [Mike] That's lieutenant girl.
- [Geronimo] Alright.
- [Crow] I put brown and
serves in this thing.
- I hope this works out because lord knows
I've just ruined my career.
- [Tom] Ah girls don't
have careers, let's go.
- [Maria] Slow down
sheriff, if anyone sees us
we must not look suspicious.
- Young lady it took a lot of guts
for you to break me out of here.
- Well we have a saying here in Malta
like your saying in America.
Only here it goes: right
is might and I believe
that getting Palermo is
the right thing to do.
- [Mike] Yeah make me some coffee.
- And I want to help get him.
- Let's hope your superintendent
Mifsud agrees with you.
- [Crow] How could I not love him?
- I doubt it.
(cheerful keyboard music)
- [Tom] Alright stop sleeping
with Davy John Stone.
- No need wake the little lady.
Let's have ourselves a
corrective interview.
- [Tom] Yes I will go
ahead on and love him.
- The Lamanna villa, know where it is?
- Yeah sure, why?
- You know where it is?
- Yes, it's one of the
nicest houses on the island
and Don Lamanna's a very
respected businessman from Rome.
- Well our friendly
bartender says different.
Now where's this guy live?
- Well you'll never get there by yourself.
I'll have to take you there.
- Just tell me where the guy lives.
- Now look I've put my career on the line
to help you get Palermo.
Now the least you can do is let me help.
- Alright, there's a pier leading up
the back way to the villa.
Now if I only had a boat.
- [Tom] A gravy boat.
- No problem.
- [Crow] Man if she was only a roast.
- [Mike] When did she change
into her leather action skirt?
- [Crow] Oh but I'm fine with it.
- Do you believe the bartender
was telling the truth?
- Yeah, this is the place alright.
- [Crow] They got all the ham you can eat
with choice of sides.
- [Tom] Alright let me
guess, he fails again
the police chief threatens
him, he gets put in jail
and it's funny.
- [Crow] (laughs)
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] (imitating suspenseful guitar)
- [Mike] Alright I'm gonna smuggle yah
in one of mah neck folds.
- You stay here.
- [Tom] (imitating synth drums)
- No way.
- [Crow] Okay then, stay there.
No stay there! There, there, there.
Stay somewhere.
(ominous music)
- [Tom] (imitating synth drums)
- [Geronimo] Told you to
stay over there, didn't I?
- [Maria] And I've got help you.
- [Geronimo] Alright keep an ear out
while I kick this door in.
- [Maria] Now wait, wait, let's try this.
- [Geronimo] What?
- [Maria] Hairpin.
- [Tom] Why would I kick a hairpin?
- [Geronimo] Well honey, I am impressed.
- [Maria] I've been doing
this since I was a kid.
- [Geronimo] This is as far as you go.
- [Maria] But I have just
proved that I can help you.
- [Geronimo] You don't even have a gun.
Now the way to help is to get
some reinforcements with some weapons.
- But I won't let you go in there alone,
you'll never come out alive.
- [Crow] Yay.
- My best to get the job done is
not havin to worry about you.
Now go on, do what I tell yah.
- [Crow] (kissing at screen)
- [Geronimo] Go on, be careful.
- [Mike] Don't team up with any
chubby Texans while I'm in here.
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom] Right into the
guard dog's kennels.
- [Crow] Gotta turn down
the pressure on that bidet.
- [Tom] Pistol whipping a
suspect: feels just like Texas.
- [Crow] Man he makes Porter
Wagner look under dressed.
(gun cocks)
- Finish your coffee Palermo.
- [Tom] Please it's cocoa.
- Maybe you'd like to join me Cowboy?
- No thanks. I had mine
in jail this evening.
That's where you'll be
having yours tomorrow.
- So this is the American
who's been causing all the trouble.
- [Crow] Would you like a robe?
- I'm very impressed sheriff.
You seem to have more lives than a cat.
You Americans
- [Mike] With your Leo-Sair.
- [Lamanna] always think
you know the answers.
But you are always wrong.
- [Crow] Lou Ferrigno looks on.
- Put down the gun.
- [Tom] But it seemed
like that's what happened
when I shot you that time.
You would never believe me.
- [Mike] I shouldn't have.
Oh no I'm gettin aroused.
(grunting)
- [Crow] (imitating choking, gagging)
- [Tom] Oh his copy of Mirabella!
- [Mike] So this isn't Il Postino, right?
- [Tom] Maybe now would be a good time
to call him a son of a!
- [Crow] I can't take you sitting on me!
I'm gonna off myself!
(straining and groaning)
- Freeze! Get up!
- [Mike] How did he buy
a styrofoam coffee table?
- [Crow] (chuckles)
- It was an accident, I didn't
mean it, it was his fault!
- He's mine. I owe him this.
You just do what you're told.
I'll take care of the family in Rome.
- [Crow] I'll take your
orders to Tony Roma's?
- You like a swim Cowboy, huh?
(grunts in pain)
- [Tom] (grunts)
It does look fun, I have to say.
- [Mike] (chuckles)
- You should have stayed
with your cows sheriff.
- [Crow] Shoulda stained my cows?
- [Tom] By killing em.
- Hey someone not hideous!
(grunts)
- [Tom] (grunts, farts, belches)
- Get on the boat Cowboy.
- Freeze!
Don't anybody move!
- [Crow] I'm Jerry Reed.
- Saw that mess upstairs.
- [Mike] What'd you guys eat?
- [Geronimo] Wilson.
You take care of the big
one, I got the little one.
- Let's not do anything hasty,
lots of people could get hurt this way.
- Palermo ain't gonna start nothin.
Are yah, yah gutless son of a.
All Palermo does is ambush people.
You're not gonna do anything
face-to-face are you Palermo?
- [Wilson] I have some questions;
I'd like to have answers.
Now that Lamanna's dead, who's gonna
pay me the rest of my money?
- [Tom] (grunts in surprise)
- [Mike] (chuckles)
- Your money is completely
safe, the family in Rome
will take care of that.
- [Mike] Oh Popeye (giggles)
- [Wilson] Sorry about this Geronimo,
nobody was supposed to get hurt.
Lamanna paid me a lot of money
to keep Mr. Palermo here out of Italy.
- [Crow] So confused and hungry.
- I thought it would be safe using a dumb
Texas sheriff like yourself.
- You figured wrong.
- Hold it right there Mr. Wilson.
- [Tom] Dennis?
- Put your gun down.
- [Mike] Me? Me? Me? Me?
(gunshot)
(screaming while flare burns)
- [Crow] Opa!
- [Mike] Horsefly on your nose, sorry.
- [Tom] Still confused, still hungry.
- I guess I should thank
you young lady. (cackles)
You just saved me $250,000 dollars.
You watch the Cowboy Foster!
- [Crow] I watch the cowboy poster! Huh?
- [Mike] He's the mobster who gives
people a stern talking to.
- [Maria] Let me go!
- [Crow] My watch is caught in your hair.
- [Palermo] (muttering viciously)
- [Tom] Just let me borrow it! Come on!
- [Crow] Yes the longtime Texas-Maltese
rivalry comes to a head.
- [Mike] If I could only get mah
sausagey fingers around his gun.
- [Tom] Ugh, Popeye.
- [Crow] I'll pick your
nose if you scream.
- [Mike] Ooh, hot hot gun, ooh ow.
- [Tom] Ew he's got au-juice all over him.
- [Crow] And now the thick, meaty
conclusion of Final Justice.
- Take it easy.
- [Mike] Or the gun gets
it, I mean the girl.
- Do it! Blow the, away.
- Don't be stupid Cowboy.
I'll blow her brains out.
- [Crow] All over the boat!
- Just throw the gun away.
- Wait a minute, let's talk.
- [Tom] I miss our little chats.
- You said somethin to Wilson
about $250,000 dollars?
- Okay, I was going to
have to pay Wilson anyhow.
Just give me the gun, we're
gonna make a deal, huh?
- You serious?
- Yeah!
- Alright, I'm puttin it away.
- [Mike] I've just had a
really hard day. (snuffles)
- (laughing) You are dumber
than I thought Cowboy.
- [Crow] Tell me about it.
- Now I can save a lot
of money with one bullet.
One!
- And I can get rid of a scum,
like you with just one bullet.
- [Tom] Ugh someone salted him,
so his juices are coming up.
- [Mike And Crow] (grunt in disgust)
- Think you can take me?
- [Mike] Yeah if I can get my mom's car.
- Go ahead on.
- [Crow] He's going aheading on-ing.
- Shoot.
(groans in pain)
- [Tom] Our hero, a big stinky cheater.
- [Mike] (chuckles) Yeah.
- Darlin, that biggun's got
- [Mike] My cheater.
- [Geronimo] my badge.
Would you get it for me?
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] What!
- [Mike] What kind of a
great last line is that?
- [Tom And Crow] (exclaim in disgust)
- [Crow] Ah you know this music makes me
want to put a triangle on my
privates and squirm around.
- [Tom] Ooh.
- [Mike] Like in the movie.
- [Crow] Like what? What
are you talking about?
- [Mike] (chuckles) Ah never mind.
- [Crow] I want to put a triangle
on my privates and squirm around.
- [Mike] Okay.
♫ you better run ♫
- [Tom] Or he'll steal your lunch!
♫ you better hide ♫
♫ your lunch ♫
♫ you better run ♫
♫ cause he's got the runs ♫
♫ cause he won't stop
till he gets his man ♫
♫ or your lunch ♫
- [Crow] Oh yeah! Woo!
Yeah, play it.
Mmm listen to that guitar solo.
I think it's by Eric Clap.
Yeah Eric Clap.
- [Mike] Hey, Joe Don's
personal prostitute
made it into the credits.
♫ takes a roast and wrap it in bacon ♫
♫ that may be true ♫
♫ but there's potatoes on the side ♫
- [Crow] Woo, yeah! Pass the gravy now!
- [Mike] You know, maybe we should
lay off the food jokes guys.
- [Crow] Yeah I guess it's not really fair
to Joe Don Baker.
- [Mike] I mean some people
metabolize just a little slower.
♫ meatballs fried in lard ♫
- [Crow] Sorry Mike, all bets are off.
- [Mike] Oh come on, now.
- [Tom And Crow] Eat, eat,
eat, eat, eat, eat, eat, eat,
munch, munch, munch, munch,
chew, chew, chew, chew,
gorge, gorge, gorge, gorge,
burp, burp, burp, burp.
♫ stuff lots of food in
your mean baby face ♫
- [Mike] Oh now you guys prepared that.
- [Crow] Come on, it's
an obvious line Mike.
♫ you'd better hide ♫
♫ pork chops, cream puffs, candy bars ♫
♫ meat sauce, cheetos, malomars ♫
♫ cause he won't stop
till he eats it all ♫
- [Mike] Yeah okay that's it, I'm goin.
You guys do your food jokes.
- [Crow] Yeah! Give me seconds baby!
- [Tom] Hoo! Hey baby
you gonna finish that?
Anyone gonna eat that last piece of cake?
Cause I will.
Ah somebody give me a napkin!
- [Crow] Hey, hey, hey where'd Mike go?
- [Tom] Mike? Mike?
- [Crow] He ditched us! Mike.
- [Tom] Where'd he go? What do I do?
(hatch slamming)
(gears clanking)
(beeping)
(engine whirring)
(chains clinking)
(wood door slamming)
(metal screeching)
(doors slamming and sealing)
(hatch locking)
(siren blaring)
- Ten seconds and counting.
- What? What's going on up here Gyp's?
- Seven seconds. Oh, it's so sad.
So sad. (whimpers)
- Whoa Mike!
- I'm ready you guys.
Boy I can't wait to see
Spooner Wisconsin again.
Servo, Crow, Gypsy so long.
I love you guys.
- Mike what are you doin in there?
- Well it's my turn to escape.
Joel got to go right after he saw
a really bad Joe Don Baker
movie, so I kinda just figured.
Well anyway I left you a plaque there with
an inspirational poem on it.
It's from my favorite movie:
Herbie Goes to Monte Carlo.
- [Tom] He's in trouble.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- Though you are small and
white, your wheels are silver
- [Tom] Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike!
and they always inspire me
I'm sorry buddy but
you're not goin anywhere.
- Nope.
- But I just suffered through a really
bad Joe Don Baker movie.
- Unrelated Mike, sorry.
You see Gypsy sent Joel back
to Earth in an escape pod
she hid in a box of hamdingers.
- Yeah.
- There are no more escape pods, Mike.
- You do know that you're sitting
in the water heater, don't you?
- Yeah, I know.
- Come on upstairs honey,
we'll make you some Swiss Miss.
- Well how about if we see a really
good Joe Don Baker movie?
- Well I think we can guarantee that's
never gonna happen Mike.
- Oh, Pearl's callin. Poor fella.
- Really, ugh.
- (cackles evily) See
now that's funny, Nelson.
Pretending you're stupid enough to think
you could ever escape me. (laughs)
And here's something else we recommend
to keep those chuckles
coming at the office.
Funny dress up day.
Workers are more light-hearted because
they are wearing whimsical expressions
of faux-individuality.
For instance, I'm wearing
wacky mismatched colors.
Whee! And Bobo what do you have on?
- Well lawgiver, I went
ahead on and took a cue
from Joe Don Baker.
Heck every day is funny
dress up day for him, Wa-Hoo!
- The resemblance is uncanny.
- [Bobo] Oh my.
- [Pearl] Why and here comes Brain Guy.
My, my you went all out
for funny dress up day.
- Funny, what?
- Your outfit.
- Oh this, no, no, no I
just have a date tonight.
Don't wait up.
(both whimper)
- Nothing will ever be funny again.
- Mother! (shudders)
(anthemic horn music)
(soaring synth tones)
- You think you can take me?
Go ahead on.
It's your move.